first the I Charles Darwin himself said
to this day the eye makes me shudder
creationists a particularly fond of the
eye because they like saying what is the
use of half an eye what's your name said
him Davina
can you put your face just down there we
need the lights down I think for this
don't but don't we and within a couple
of decades they had evolved and
completely new diet and that didn't but
that to change their jaws even changed
their stomachs and they now got stomach
valves in just a couple of decades just
think what could be achieved in a
million years a hundred million years we
don't we don't have proper understanding
of what value has been encoded in
religious belief and so we are not in a
position to replace it with other things
that serve the same functions there was
wisdom encoded in ancient belief
structures that we have not yet
understood and we are gonna we are I
think it is inevitable that we will harm
ourselves in the process of discovering
where value was hidden why would they
have any wisdom about the origin of the
world or the origin of anything else
that particular myth is the myth that
just by sheer chance the judeo-christian
myth happens to have come to our
civilization there are thousands of
myths in the world none of them are any
better than any of the others some of
them are not more poetic than that one
these belief systems have flourished
because they have facilitated the
interests of the creatures involved our
belief systems are built around
evolutionary success
[Music]
you